Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  - Accession A97-11
    - Shriver, Dr. Donald W., Jr., 1968-1983 (Box 68)
    - Dallas Blue Ribbon Group - Perkins School, 1987-1989 (Box 68)
    - Perkins School of Theology Executive Board, 1986-1991 (2 Folders) (Box 68)
    - A - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 68)
    - AAR/SRL, 1986-1989 (Box 68)
    - Abingdon Press, 1986-1989 (Box 68)
    - Abraham, Billy, 1988-1992 (Box 68)
    - Adams, Dough, 1983-1990 (2 folders) (Box 68)
    - Admin. Assistants to Bishops, 1989 (Box 68)
    - AIDS Conference, Cambridge, MA, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
    - AIDS and Religion, North American Context, 1987-1991 (Box 68)
    - Alban Institute, 1989-1993 (Box 68)
    - Albemarle District - Spirit Fest, 1986 (Box 68)
    - Aldridge, Julian, 1987-1989 (Box 68)
    - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center, 1986-1989 (Box 68)
    - Asbury UMC Centennial, 1977, 1993 (Box 68)
    - Ashanti Gold Weights, 1980-1988 (Box 68)
    - Ashland Theological Seminary Commencement, 1987 (Box 68)
    - Barclitt Scholarship, 1986 (Box 68)
    - Robert Bellah Dinner. 1986 (Box 68)
    - Bethea, Joe, 1972-1987 (Box 68)
    - Biggs, Walter A., (Funeral Service) 1989 (Box 68)
    - Divinity School Faculty Minutes, 1926-1974 (32 Folders) (Box 69)
    - B - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (3 Folders) (Box 70)
    - Bishops Role in the United Methodist Church, 1990 (Box 70)
    - Borgen, Peder, Professor, 1983, 1988 (Box 70)
    - Boston University Sesquicentennial, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Baptist Alliance, 1988-1989 (Box 70)
    - Brasher, Larry, 1985-1990 (Box 70)
    - Browning, Don - Visit, 1990 (Box 70)
    - Bryan Foundation, James E. and Mary Z., 1986 (Box 70)
    - Methodist Church of Brazil, 1990 (Box 70)
    - C - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (4 Folders) (Box 70)
    - Can Capitalism Be Christian? 1986 (Box 70)
    - Cartwright, Michael, 1984-1990 (Box 70)
    - Center for the Study of Religion and Economics, 1987 (Box 70)
    - Center for Studies in the Wesleyan Tradition, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Center on Religion and Society, 1987-1989 (Box 70)
    - Charlesworth, Jean H., 1985-1986 (Box 70)
    - Durham Youth Home Dinner, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Christian Century Review on Apologia, 1988 (Box 70)
    - Society of Christian Ethics, 1988 (Box 70)
    - Cokesbury - Dennis M. Campbell, 1984-1989 (Box 70)
    - Columbia District Seminar, Myrtle Beach, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Corbett, Marion, 1985-1991 (Box 70)
    - Covenant Center - Morganton, NC, 1985-1987 (Box 70)
    - Covenant Disciplship Group, 1988-1990 (Box 70)
    - Dempster Fellowship, 1987 (Box 70)
    - Cully, Iris V. and Kendig Brubaker, 1985-1987 (Box 70)
    - Cunningham, Merrimon, 1985-1987 (Box 70)
    - Darr, Katheryn P. - Visit, 1993 (Box 70)
    - Davis, Patricia Howery - Visit, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Davis, Russell - Visit, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Deal, Claude V. - Installation, York Chapel, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
    - Deerfield Academy, Massachusetts. 1991-1993 (Box 70)
    - Disciples Divinity House, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Drew University, Celebration, 1992 (Box 70)
    - Duke, Angier B. - Visit, 1989 (Box 70)
    - D - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 70)
    - Durham Declaration Project, 1990 (Box 70)
    - E - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 70)
    - Eli, George, 1986-1988 (Box 70)
    - Elizabeth City Lay Rally, 1991-1992 (Box 70)
    - Episcopal Dialogue - Raleigh, 1992 (Box 70)
    - Episcopal Candidates, 1984 (Box 70)
    - Episcopal Churchwomen Preach at St. Phillips, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Epp, Prof. Eldon Jay, 1986-1987 (Box 70)
    - Evans, Mark, 1987 (Box 70)
    - University of Evansville, Indiana, 1988 (Box 70)
    - F - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 70)
    - Wedding of Randolph Few and Emily Oliver, 1987 (Box 71)
    - Finch-Hunt Lecture, 1989-1992 (Box 71)
    - Florida Conference - Institute of Preaching, 1989-1990 (Box 71)
    - Florida Development Trip, 1987 (Box 71)
    - Florida Southern, Baccalaureate, 1986 (Box 71)
    - Ellwood, Eric L., 1986 (Box 71)
    - Foundation for Theological Education, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
    - Franklin, William, 1990 (Box 71)
    - Friendly, Fred W., 1985 (Box 71)
    - Friends Center Meeting, 1988 (Box 71)
    - Front St. United Methodist Church, Burlington, NC, 1991 (Box 71)
    - Fulcher, J. Rodneym 1987-1988 (Box 71)
    - Fund for Theological Education (Minorities), 1983-1990 (Box 71)
    - G - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
    - Graymoor Ecumenical Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
    - Garrison, Peggy L. T. - Visit, 1987 (Box 71)
    - Gibbons, Ronald - Visity, 1985 (Box 71)
    - Gichaara, Rev. Johnathan, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
    - Good News Magazine, 1986-1990 (Box 71)
    - Gopal, Arun, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
    - Grant, Jacquelinem 1977-1987 (Box 71)
    - Greensboro College - Jean Fortner Ward Lecture, 1988-1989 (Box 71)
    - Grose, Dr. George B., 1983-1990 (Box 71)
    - Grousbeck, H. Irving, 1990-1991 (Box 71)
    - Guilford County Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 71)
    - H - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (3 Folders) (Box 71)
    - Harper, Steve - Visit, 1986-1990 (Box 71)
    - Hartford, CT., 1991 (Box 71)
    - Hensley, Bernard, 1985 (Box 71)
    - Heydenreich, Jon, 1986-1988 (Box 71)
    - High Point College - National Committee of Future of HPC, 1986-1989 (Box 71)
    - Holston Conference, Gatlinburg, TN., 1988 (Box 71)
    - Hope, Sam - Witness for Peace, 1989 (Box 71)
    - First UMC - Houston, TX, 1987 (Box 71)
    - Hutter, Reinhard, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
    - I - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 71)
    - Italy, 1992 (Box 71)
    - J - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 71)
    - Jamestown UMC - Preach, 1986 (Box 71)
    - East Carolin University - Jarvis Lectures, 1992 (Box 71)
    - Jones, L. Gregory, 1986-1991 (Box 71)
    - The E. Stanley Jones Fund, undated (Box 71)
    - Jones, Hamill D., 1982-1992 (Box 71)
    - Jordan, Robert and Sarahm 1984-1987 (Box 71)
    - K - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 71)
    - Kacmarcik, Frank - Visit, 1977-1986 (Box 71)
    - Stover-Ward Lecture, Kansas City, MO., 1991-1992 (Box 71)
    - Kim, Kwanlyun - Visitm 1984-1987 (Box 71)
    - Fountain City Methodist Church, Knoxville, TN., 1982-1986 (Box 71)
    - Kimbrough, Steven, 1985-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 71)
    - Kirby, Dr. Wallace, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
    - Kresge, Stanley S., 1980-1987 (Box 71)
    - Kwansei Gakuin University - Japanm 1986 (Box 71)
    - L - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
    - Labyrinth Press, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Lake Junaluska Seminary Rentals, 1986-1992 (Box 72)
    - Langley, Delores, 1986-1987 (Box 72)
    - Langston, Craig, 1990-1992 (Box 72)
    - The Leadership Council - Paul Stames, 1990-1991 (Box 72)
    - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1978-1992 (Box 72)
    - Lim, Isaac, 1987-1989 (Box 72)
    - Long, Steve (Prelims), 1989-1990 (Box 72)
    - Lutheran Theological Southern Seminary, 1986 (Box 72)
    - Lynchburg District - CEU Seminar, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Lynn, Robert (Lilly Endowment) - Visit, 1991 (Box 72)
    - K. Brynolf Lyon - Presentation, 1987-1988 (Box 72)
    - M - Misc. Correspondencem 1985-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 72)
    - Mc. - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 72)
    - Mainous, Arch, 1985-1989 (Box 72)
    - Marsden, George M., 1986-1992 (Box 72)
    - Meador, Keith, 1984-1988 (Box 72)
    - Medlock, Scott, 1986-1991 (Box 72)
    - Meeks, M. Douglas, 1985-1986 (Box 72)
    - Methodist College Commencement, 1990 (Box 72)
    - Milford, Brian, 1985-1990 (Box 72)
    - Holy Week Services - Jackson, MS., 1987 (Box 72)
    - Mission Resource Center, 1987-1988 (Box 72)
    - Mission Theology Conference, 1989 (Box 72)
    - Mitchum, Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth E., 1985-1987 (Box 72)
    - Mississippi Conference, 1986 (Box 72)
    - Moore, Steve, 1986-1991 (Box 72)
    - Morton, Steven C., 1986-1987 (Box 72)
    - First UMC, Morganton, NC, 1985-1986 (Box 72)
    - Moessner, Jeanne S. - Visit, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Myers Park UMC, 1989 (Box 72)
    - Methodists Organized for Religious and Ethical Concerns (MORE), 1986 (Box 72)
    - N - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 72)
    - National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1993 (Box 72)
    - Native Americans, 1991 (Box 72)
    - Nausner, Helmut, 1984-1987 (Box 72)
    - Nairobi - Dean Campbell, 1986 (2 Folders) (Box 72)
    - National Humanities Center RTP, 1986-1989 (Box 72)
    - Naylor, Thomas H. and Corporate Responsibility, 1985-1989 (Box 72)
    - NEH Seminar Members, 1985 (Box 72)
    - Navy Chaplains (Th. M.), 1987 (Box 72)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Eugene Needham, 1985-1988 (Box 72)
    - Neuger, Christie - Visit, 1987 (Box 72)
    - National Foundation for the Study of Religion and Economics, 1986-1987 (Box 72)
    - Theological Education and Moral Formation, 1988-1990 (Box 72)
    - Niles, Dr. H. Clifton (Meth. Church in Caribbean), 1987-1988 (Box 72)
    - Newsom, Carol, 1989 (Box 72)
    - N.C. Wesleyan College - Inauguration of President Garner, 1988 (Box 72)
    - Noll, Mark, 1987 (Box 72)
    - N.C. Council of Churches, 1984 (Box 72)
    - N.C. Sane/Freeze (Campaign for Global Security), 1989-1990 (Box 72)
    - North Indiana Conference Ordination Service, 1990 (Box 72)
    - Nuclear Policy Statement, 1986 (Box 72)
    - O - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 72)
    - O'Brien, Julia - Visit, 1993 (Box 72)
    - West Ohio Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
    - Dayton, Ohio, 1988-1990 (Box 72)
    - Ohio - Columbus South District, 1985-1988 (Box 72)
    - The Eight Oxford Institute of Methodist Theological Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 72)
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1991 (Box 72)
    - P - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1992 (2 Folders) (Box 72)
    - Panos - International Consultation on Churches and AIDS, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
    - N.C. Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1985 (Box 72)
    - Pacific School of Religion Summer Session, 1984-1985 (Box 72)
    - Paschal, Wade - Visit, 1990 (Box 72)
    - Professional Standards Program, 1987 (Box 72)
    - Patton, John H. - Visit, 1988 (Box 73)
    - Pax Worldfund, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 73)
    - Peace College Orientation, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Pittsburgh-East District Conference, Monroeville, PA, 1989 (Box 73)
    - Pierce Collection, 1981-1982 (Box 73)
    - Pollard, Alton, 1989 (Box 73)
    - Quick, Dr. William, 1986-1989 (Box 73)
    - R - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1991 (3 folders) (Box 73)
    - R. J. Reynolds, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
    - Richey, Russell - Visit, 1986 (Box 73)
    - Robinson, Thomas A., 1989 (Box 73)
    - Roche, Robert, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Rock, Judith, 1985-1986 (Box 73)
    - Ross Johnston and Kersting, Inc., 1987 (Box 73)
    - S - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1991 (4 folders) (Box 73)
    - Society of New Testament Scholars (SNTS), 1986 (Box 73)
    - St. George's College, Jersusalem, 1985-1986 (Box 73)
    - Scarritt Visits, 1986-1987 (Box 73)
    - Scarritt Graduate School, 1985-1986 (Box 73)
    - Scott, Dr. Julius S., Jr., 1982-1988 (Box 73)
    - Seminary Week - Lake Junaluska, 1982-1984 (Box 73)
    - Seven Churches of Methodism, 1985 (Box 73)
    - Siegert, Elizabeth, 1992 (Box 73)
    - Smith, Alma and Shelton - Final Arrangements, 1987 (Box 73)
    - The Society of Christian Ethics, 1987-1988 (Box 73)
    - South Africa, 1985 (Box 73)
    - South Carolina Conference - Smoke Kanipe, 1991 (Box 73)
    - Southeastern Baptist Seminary, 1988-1989 (Box 73)
    - Southeastern Dinner - Wake Forest, 1982-1988 (Box 73)
    - Soviet Clergymen - Visit, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Spartanburg County Medical Society, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Stallworth, Paul T., 1987-1990 (Box 73)
    - Stedman, W.D., 1976-1991 (Box 73)
    - Struehrenberg, Paul, 1991 (Box 73)
    - Surin, Kenneth, 1987-1988 (Box 73)
    - T - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1991 (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Tanner, James T., 1981-1988 (Box 73)
    - Texas Conference Pastor's School - Houston, TX, 1986 (Box 73)
    - Texas Tech, 1984 (Box 73)
    - Theological Institutions related to the World Methodist Church, 1985 (Box 73)
    - Third World Development and Multinational Corporation, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Thomas, James B., 1986-1990 (Box 73)
    - Trimble, Martin Paul, 1986-1989 (Box 73)
    - Tyson, John H., 1985-1989 (Box 73)
    - Ulanov, Ann - Visit, 1987 (Box 73)
    - National United Methodist Seminarians, 1985 (Box 73)
    - Union Theological Seminary Review, 1987 (Box 73)
    - UM Publishing House, 1984-1991 (Box 73)
    - University of Durham, England, 1984-1987 (Box 74)
    - Visiting Committees of University Divinity Schools, 1983 (Box 74)
    - V - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 74)
    - W - Misc. Correspondence, 1985-1991 (4 Folders) (Box 74)
    - Waits, Dean Jim L., 1987-1990 (Box 74)
    - Wake Forest Divinity School Discussions, 1989-1990 (Box 74)
    - Waldensians of Valdese, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
    - Wallace, Charles I., Jr., 1985 (Box 74)
    - Walters-Bugbee, Chris, 1983-1990 (Box 74)
    - Whanger, Dr. Alan, 1982-1991 (Box 74)
    - Ware and Associates, undated (Box 74)
    - Weber, John - Memorial Service, 1992 (Box 74)
    - Weber, Mike - Ministerial Relations Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 74)
    - John Wesley Fellows Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 74)
    - Wesley College, England, 1978-1986 (Box 74)
    - John Wesley Research Fellowship Wesley College, Bristol, England, 1984-1985 (Box 74)
    - Speaker for the Wesleymen Program, Norfolk, VA, 1990-1991 (Box 74)
    - West, John Cameron, 1983-1991 (Box 74)
    - Westminster College, Oxford, England, 1990 (Box 74)
    - Williams, A. Morris-Endowment Dinner, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Bowman Gray of Medicine - Wake Forest Univ., 1989-1990 (Box 74)
    - Witherington, Ben, 1985-1990 (Box 74)
    - Worship Committee, 1990 (Box 74)
    - Y - Misc. Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 74)
    - Yarborough, Yogi, 1984-1990 (Box 74)
    - Z - Misc. Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 74)
    - University of Zimbabwe, 1984-1986 (Box 74)
    - Zondervan Publishing House, 1990 (Box 74)
    - Academic Programs, 1986 (Box 74)
    - Admissions Director Search, 1988 (Box 74)
    - National Alumni Council, 1989-1991 (Box 74)
    - Alumni Association, 1985-1989 (Box 74)
    - Annual Fund, 1983-1989 (Box 74)
    - Arts Committee, 1978-1986 (Box 74)
    - Baccalaureate - Div. School Graduation, 1982-1987 (Box 74)
    - Believers' Church - Meeting, 1989 (Box 74)
    - Black Church Affairs, 1985-1987 (Box 74)
    - Bowl Game - Birmingham, 1989 (Box 74)
    - Bulletin Information, 1987 (Box 74)
    - Chaplaincy Search Committee, 1986 (Box 74)
    - Kenneth W. Clark Lecture Program, 1984-1985 (Box 74)
    - Kenneth W. Clark Lectures, 1986-1990 (Box 74)
    - Continuing Education, 1986-1988 (Box 74)
    - Closing Convocation, 1989 (Box 74)
    - Opening Convocation, 1989 (Box 74)
    - Opening Convocation, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Closing Convocation, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Opening Convocation, 1987 (Box 74)
    - Closing Convocation, 1987 (Box 74)
    - Computers for Continuing Education, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
    - Computer for Development, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
    - Opening Convocation, 1986 (Box 74)
    - Closing Convocation, 1986 (Box 74)
    - Opening Convocation, 1985 (Box 74)
    - Closing Convocation, 1985 (Box 74)
    - Opening Convocation, 1984 (Box 74)
    - Closing Convocation, 1984 (Box 75)
    - Opening Convocation, 1983 (Box 75)
    - Closing Convocation, 1983 (Box 75)
    - Course of Study School, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1986 (Box 75)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1985 (Box 75)
    - Dates to Remember, 1987-1990 (Box 75)
    - Deans Advisory Council, 1982-1983 (Box 75)
    - The Dean's Letter, 1986-1991 (Box 75)
    - Dean's Club Dinner, 1983-1988 (Box 75)
    - Duke-Bonn Colloquy, 1983-1985 (2 Folders) (Box 75)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award, 1973-1986 (Box 75)
    - Divinity School Fellowship, 1984-1988 (Box 75)
    - Duke Disciples, 1987 (Box 75)
    - Duke Endowment, 1983-1990 (Box 75)
    - Field Education, 1983-1989 (Box 75)
    - Economic Justice Seminar, 1988 (Box 75)
    - Consultation on the Priority of Evangelism, 1983 (Box 75)
    - Faculty Research Interests (Box 75)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Faculty Retreat - National Humanities Center, 1988 (Box 75)
    - Faculty Retreat, 1987 (Box 75)
    - Faculty Pot Luck Supper, 1986-1989 (Box 75)
    - Faculty Wives Luncheon, 1986-1989 (Box 75)
    - Field Enrollment Data, 1982-1985 (Box 75)
    - Financial Aid Matters, 1983-1990 (Box 75)
    - Foundations - General, 1990 (Box 75)
    - Graduate Program in Religion, 1983-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 75)
    - Graduate Assistantships, 1981-1983 (Box 75)
    - Conference on Medicine and Society, 1984 (Box 75)
    - Staff Retreat, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Small Church Capital Fund Program, 1983 (Box 75)
    - Grants, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Grievances - Divinity Students, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
    - Georgia Harkness Scholarships, 1983-1990 (Box 75)
    - Honor Code Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 75)
    - Hymnal Project, 1986-1988 (Box 75)
    - Inclusive Language Guidelines, 1985-1990 (Box 75)
    - Reception for International Group, 1986-1989 (Box 75)
    - Jameson Jones Lectures, 1985-1989 (Box 75)
    - Jameson Jones Practicing Award, 1983-1990 (Box 75)
    - Kearns Dinner, 1986-1992 (Box 75)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Lectures, 1984-1990 (Box 75)
    - Lecture Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 75)
    - Masters of Theological Studies Curch Administration, 1987-1989 (Box 75)
    - Myers, Eric - Faculty Governance, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
    - Ministerial Division, 1984 (Box 75)
    - New Divinity Maintenance, 1985-1988 (Box 75)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1990, undated (Box 75)
    - New Testament Search Committee, 1983, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Press Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
    - The J. M. Ormond Center, 1987-1990 (Box 75)
    - Pastoral Care, 1985-1989 (Box 75)
    - Parents Fund Committee Members, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
    - Peru Exchange Program, 1988-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Photos - Opening Convocation, 1988 (Box 76)
    - Photos - Misc., undated (2 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Photos - Divinity Faculty, undated (2 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Planning Document, 1987 (Box 76)
    - Press Releases, 1985-1990 (Box 76)
    - Registry Manual of Procedures, 1986-1989 (Box 76)
    - Scholarship Recipients, 1983-1984 (Box 76)
    - Scholarships - Trial Year, 1988-1991 (Box 76)
    - Seminarians (Contemporary), 1987-1990 (Box 76)
    - Senior Class Banquet, 1983-1984 (Box 76)
    - Seven Churches of Methodism, 1985 (Box 76)
    - Sexual Harassment/Graduate Religion, 1989 (Box 76)
    - Shackford Endowment Fund, 1986 (Box 76)
    - 60th Anniversary of the Div. School, 1986 (Box 76)
    - Student Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 76)
    - Students' Organization Luncheon, 1987 (Box 76)
    - SRA Constitution and Info., 1985-1989 (Box 76)
    - Gardner C. Taylor Lectures, 1987-1988 (Box 76)
    - Tenured Faculty, 1987-1990 (Box 76)
    - Theological Division, 1983-1991 (Box 76)
    - Th. D. Proposal, 1983-1989 (Box 76)
    - The Women's Center, 1984-1991 (Box 76)
    - AAR Ad Hoc Committee - Atlanta, GA., 1990-1994 (Box 76)
    - Abingdon Press, 1990-1994 (Box 76)
    - Adams, Doug (Art), 1991-1994 (Box 76)
    - Augsburger, David (Pastoral Care), 1992-1993 (Box 76)
    - B - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1994 (2 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Conference on the Meaning of Baptism, 1989-1990 (Box 76)
    - Beeson School of Divinity, Birmingham, AL., 1994 (Box 76)
    - Boswell Lectures, Dallas, TX., 1989-1990 (Box 76)
    - C - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 76)
    - Sarah and Phillip Connolly - Visit, 1992 (Box 76)
    - Cartwright, Michael, 1991-1994 (Box 76)
    - The Christian Century, 1990-1993 (Box 76)
    - Christian Enrichment School - Ft. Myers, FL., 1993-1994 (Box 76)
    - Class Leader Seminar, 1993 (Box 76)
    - Cokesbury, 1991-1992 (Box 76)
    - Columbus, OH., 1991 (Box 76)
    - Cowan, Ivy, 1967-1988 (Box 76)
    - Cunningham, Merrimon, 1991-1995 (Box 76)
    - D - Misc. Correspondencem 1990-1993 (Box 76)
    - Dickson, Kenny, 1993-1994 (Box 76)
    - Disciple Bible Study, 1995 (Box 76)
    - Doser Designs - Trust Project, 1992 (2 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1990-1995 (Box 76)
    - E - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 76)
    - F - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 77)
    - F.H.I. Meetings and Board of Directors, 1990-1993 (Box 77)
    - Foundation for Evangelism, 1986-1993 (2 Folders) (Box 77)
    - G - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - Gomes, Peter, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - H - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - Hale, Dr. Joe - World Meth. Council, 1985-1993 (Box 77)
    - Harper, Steve, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - Hillerbrand, Hans J., 1986-1992 (Box 77)
    - J - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Jenkins, David Oli, 1987-1993 (Box 77)
    - Jones, L. Gregory, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - K - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Kimbrough, Steven, 1991 (Box 77)
    - L - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric, 1990-1991 (Box 77)
    - Lovin, Robin W., 1985-1992 (Box 77)
    - M - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - Mc - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - McNeill, William W., 1992 (Box 77)
    - N - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - N.C. Christian Advocate, 1985-1993 (Box 77)
    - P - Misc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 77)
    - Palmer, Ruth - 1987-1993 (Box 77)
    - R - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - S - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Toole, David, 1989-1993 (Box 77)
    - Tyson, Rev. John H., 1990-1993 (Box 77)
    - U - Misc. Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 77)
    - Udoh, Fabian, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - U. Meth. Publishing House, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - W - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Wimmer, John - Visit, 1993 (Box 77)
    - Young, Norman, 1983-1991 (Box 77)
    - Yarborough, Yogi, 1990-1992 (Box 77)
    - X, Y, Z - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Bethea, Bishop Joseph B., 1988-1995 (Box 77)
    - Choy, Bishop Wilbur W. Y., 1973, 1979 (Box 77)
    - Dixon, Bishop Ernest T., Jr., 1991 (Box 77)
    - Galloway, Bishop Paul V., 1965-1982 (Box 77)
    - Garrison, Bishop Edwin R., 1972-1995 (Box 77)
    - Harmon, Bishop Nolan B., 1959-1986 (Box 77)
    - Henley, Bishop James W., 1966-1967 (Box 77)
    - Robertson, Bishop Frank L., 1981-1986 (Box 77)
    - Short, Bishop Roy, 1965-1989 (Box 77)
    - Webb, Bishop Lance, 1979 (Box 77)
    - Wunderlich, Bishop Friederich, 1959 (Box 77)
    - Board of Visitors, 1986-1990 (5 Folders) (Box 77)
    - Board of Visitors, 1983-1991 (3 Folders) (Box 78)
    - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1983-1989 (2 Folders) (Box 78)
    - Arcus, David, 1985-1989 (Box 78)
    - Askren, Carter, 1988-1990 (Box 78)
    - Bailey, Lloyd, 1982-1990 (Box 78)
    - Brown, Wes, 1982-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 78)
    - Baker Collection, 1979-1990 (Box 78)
    - Berger, Teresa, 1983-1990 (Box 78)
    - Crenshaw, James L., 1985-1990 (Box 78)
    - Duke Sesquicentennial - Trinity, NC, 1988 (Box 79)
    - Duke News Service, 1985 (Box 79)
    - Duke Seminar, 1990 (Box 79)
    - Duke Tuition Grant Program, 1985 (Box 79)
    - Reception and Service for Elected Officials, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Dates to Remember, 1984-1991 (Box 79)
    - Faculty Handbook Revision Meeting, 1986 (Box 79)
    - Facilities, 1989-1994 (Box 79)
    - Faculty Nomenclature, 1988-1989 (Box 79)
    - Faculty Voting, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Financial Aid, 1986-1991 (Box 79)
    - Blimd Letters of Reference, 1984 (Box 79)
    - Fleishman, Joel, 1986-1990 (Box 79)
    - Football Misc., 1986-1990 (Box 79)
    - Founders' Society Dinner, 1989-1991 (Box 79)
    - Founders' Dinner - Div School, 1991 (Box 79)
    - Founders' Day, 1987-1991 (2 Folders) (Box 79)
    - Founders' Day - Preach in Duke Chapel, 1986 (Box 79)